♪If I am gone from this world,
will the dark night collapse?♪
♪If I never return
to guard by your side♪
♪If I seal away our encounter
and erase all trace♪
♪Like endless snow
falling into the deep sea♪
♪This life is but a fleeting illusion,
yet it gave me courage♪
♪Love is a miracle♪
=Spring Over Phoenix Pond=
(Adapted from Qin An'an's
"Spring Over Phoenix Pond")
=Episode 7=
Your Highness.
Your Highness,
thank you for saving my life.
I heard you were ill for a long time,
but now you seem fully recovered.
Congratulations, Your Highness.
How did you manage to
get yourself into such a mess?
Has Qi Yuan returned to the residence?
Your Highness, you know Qi...
I ask,
and you answer.
Yes.
Qi Yuan has returned.
Your Highness,
I know Qi Yuan inside and out.
No matter how you want to deal with her,
I can help you.
Zhuque,
take her back and train her well.
Besides,
it's time to activate
our other hidden pawn
in the Qi Residence.
(I treated you with sincerity,)
(yet you caused my death
on the eve of my enthronement.)
This time,
don't even think
about escaping my grasp.
Why does my shoulder hurt so suddenly?
Could Prince Qi...
Is he...
(Marquis Yongping Residence)
Your Highness,
news came from the Eastern Palace.
Someone indeed added an extra herb
to the Crown Prince's decoction.
I asked the imperial physician.
Long-term consumption of this herb
will erode the heart channels
and lead to death from weakness.
Who could be so vicious?
Have someone secretly replace that herb.
Don't alert the enemy.
We must find out who is behind this.
Understood.
Qi Yuan...
How did you know
about my father's medicine?
Just how many secrets are you hiding?
(Han Yue'e, Qi Yuan's cousin)
(Your Highness,)
(I will not disappoint you.)
(Your Highness Prince Qi)
Father, Mother,
why didn't you tell me
you were returning?
I could have gone to welcome you.
Who is behind the scenes
manipulating Qi Zhao
(Old Marquis, Qi Yuan's grandfather)
into doing those absurd things?
Greetings, Grandfather and Grandmother.
Grandfather.
Grandmother.
(Old Marquise, Qi Yuan's grandmother)
You may leave.
Yuan,
come.
Come here.
Tell me,
were your adoptive parents good to you?
No.
I suffered hunger and cold,
beatings and verbal abuse.
When I was gravely ill,
I was even branded
with the scalding bottom of a bowl.
Yuan,
you have suffered so much.
So you harmed
three lives at the estate?
Yes.
Killing outsiders would be justified
since they insulted you.
Qi Zhao is your
biological brother, though.
How could you bring yourself to do it?
You even made it a massive scandal,
ruining the reputation of the Qis.
Since you have found out
the truth of this matter,
you must also know
what they did to me.
How dare you!
Do you think
because you are of Qi blood,
I won't punish you?
If you insist,
I am willing to take the punishment.
However, I beg for a chance
to make up for my mistakes.
Nonsense.
The Qi family's reputation is ruined.
How can you restore it?
Reputation is merely icing on the cake.
Imperial favor
is the true foundation of the Qi family.
The Eldest Princess
living in seclusion in the mountains
is His Majesty's deep regret.
If our family resolves
this regret for His Majesty,
who would dare bring up
today's scandal again?
Can you really
invite the Eldest Princess
to attend this welcome ceremony?
If I fail,
I will willingly accept punishment.
Very well.
If you break your word,
I will hand you over
to the Court of Judicial Review
to settle the capital charges
hanging over your head.
(It seems for this welcome ceremony,)
(I must secure
the Eldest Princess no matter what.)
Young Lady Qi,
what brings you here?
When Your Highness goes
to invite the Eldest Princess today,
if you run into obstacles,
just hand her this food box.
Before I help you,
shouldn't you tell me
how you knew my father was poisoned?
It's a long story
and involves many people.
When the welcome ceremony ends,
I will tell you everything.
Is that true?
It is.
Alright.
I'll trust you this once.
By the way,
do not sneak a bite.
Yam starch baos?
(Prince Qi Residence)
(Qi Yuan's welcome ceremony
will be held as scheduled.)
(Prince Jing has agreed)
(to help her invite
the Eldest Princess.)
Qi Yuan,
so what if Xiao Yunting helps you?
Whether the Eldest Princess
shows up or not,
you won't be able to pull off
this welcome ceremony.
Zhuque,
deliver this invitation to Father.
Yes.
Qi Yuan,
I will make you wander in exile
just like in our past life,
entirely at my mercy.
Who cares if you refuse?
I will force your hand anyway.
After such a huge scandal
in the Qi family,
how dare they throw
a grand welcome ceremony?
Didn't they say the Eldest Princess
is coming today?
I really can't believe it.
How many years has it been
since she came down the mountain?
Even the Emperor couldn't persuade her.
What makes
a wild country girl think she can?
The Qis are about to make
a huge fool of themselves again.
You actually
put your trust in that girl?
She causes trouble every day,
making our whole family
a laughingstock in public.
Watch your mouth.
Marquis,
the auspicious hour has arrived.
Do you think...
Until our honored guest arrives,
it is not an auspicious hour.
Understood.
The auspicious hour is about to pass.
Why hasn't the Eldest Princess
arrived yet?
That's right,
what's taking her so long?
Everyone,
it's a long way from Baiyun Temple.
Perhaps Her Highness was delayed
on the road.
Please stay calm.
Be patient.
If the Eldest Princess doesn't show up,
it's going to be
so embarrassing for you.
♪How I wish to hold
onto this fleeting warmth♪
♪How I wish to live
this life only for you♪
♪When memories sink
and the heart settles♪
♪Forgetting life, death,
parting, and reunion♪
♪How I wish to stay
only in the moment with you♪
♪Anchoring myself by your side♪